<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Websites on My New Hugo Site</title><link>http://localhost:1313/website/</link><description>Recent content in Websites on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/website/archeoastronomy/moon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/website/archeoastronomy/moon/</guid><description>&lt;p>Im surprised I didn&amp;rsquo;t already have a section for this. I think I finally somewhat understand declinations of the moon.
Declination in itself is a simple idea: it&amp;rsquo;s the vertical angle between the (line doing directly up? Idk the name)
So sun declination through the year ranges from 23N to 23S&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Moon is more sporadic due to its angled orbit. There&amp;rsquo;s an 18 year cycle which changes max declination from to 28.smth&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>3 body problem</title><link>http://localhost:1313/website/reviews/3-body-problem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/website/reviews/3-body-problem/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://poetryinphysics.wordpress.com/2016/11/09/a-physicist-responds-to-the-three-body-problem/">https://poetryinphysics.wordpress.com/2016/11/09/a-physicist-responds-to-the-three-body-problem/&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ok the book really picked up in the last 3rd, I was totally wrong. Now I&amp;rsquo;ll have to finish the trilogy! They still have a few hundred years to go until they encounter the aliens.
I was thinking more about scifi vs fantasy and I think they are pretty similar! Except scifi aesthetics sometimes make dreaming concepts very fun. It reminds me of getting high and doing my math homework. All those multidimensional structures coming into place, ready for me to think about them as I&amp;rsquo;m going to sleep.
A core concept later in the book is making a computer out of a single proton. I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you about it next time. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult for me to comment on feasibility but it sure is fun to think about.
I guess scifi has a lot of lore built-in which comes from high school/early college science classes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>audio journaling</title><link>http://localhost:1313/website/audio/audio-journaling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/website/audio/audio-journaling/</guid><description>&lt;p>The idea with audio journaling is the same with journaling - explore your feelings in a freeform way; like musical improvisation, rather than composition.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="observation">
 Observation
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#observation">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Get a recording device; ideally, not your phone, but phone is fine too. Just set it to airplane mode&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Go outside. Pick a setting you know well which inspires you or go to a new place.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Be in that place, allow yourself to steep in the experience. Treat it as a test tube, notice details&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Home</title><link>http://localhost:1313/website/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/website/home/</guid><description>&lt;p>I am convinced that internet has been colonized in an odd and somewhat unnatural way. Let&amp;rsquo;s maintain our own individual online gardens, here&amp;rsquo;s mine.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="currently-reading">
 Currently Reading
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#currently-reading">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>[[personal museums]] - an extension of an earlier &amp;ldquo;mediums for capturing memory&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>growth and development; no universal &amp;ldquo;adult toolkit&amp;rdquo; of skills. Missing &amp;ldquo;essential competencies&amp;rdquo; since they were assumed to be resolved by age and not effort - [[concept of adulthood as competency]]&lt;/li>
&lt;li>writing more letters to people, somehow I find just the writing process itself very soothing; it brings me joy to think about the fact that I am giving both myself and others a reason to put their thoughts on paper and send them off to be processed by someone else. Just like music is not meant to be constrained to rooms in which we tend top practice it alone, until perfection; speech should not necessarily wait to be perfected until it is shared.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Learning French</title><link>http://localhost:1313/website/other/learning-french/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/website/other/learning-french/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="classes">
 Classes
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#classes">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>